

DARIA COLGECEN

Location: Ankara, Turkey
Phone: +90 545 189 82 52
Email: tdary98@icloud.com

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dariacolgecen/

SUMMARY

A data analyst with Master's degree in Social Science and experience in data analysis and digital marketing. Skilled in data collection from different sources, processing, analysis and visualization using cloud-based business intelligence and data management software such as Clicdata, Digital Ocean and automating processes using Google Apps Script as well as creating alert systems in Slack.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Data Analyst, Al Digital

July 2023 - Present

As the only Data Analyst for a distinct brand within Al Digital, I manage the entire ELT process, collaborate
with AdOps and Sales teams to optimize campaigns, and utilize Python and SQL to analyze large datasets
and generate insights. I created over 20 dashboards for campaign monitoring and developed alert systems
in Slack for timely communication. I also identified opportunities for automation and streamlined processes
to reduce manual work for the AdOps team.

Export Account Manager, Cevik Destek

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

International Investment and Trade Consulting (Ankara)

- Established new channels for business development through export of goods and services.
- · Achieved sales goals and service targets by cultivating and securing new customer relationships.

Lead Consultant, Ministry of Economic Development of Russia

Oct 2019 - Jun 2022

- Analyzed the financial statements of more than 300 international projects.
- Took part in organization of interregional forums (Azerbaijan, Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan), and intergovernmental meetings (China, Turkey, Mongolia).
- I was a deputy member of the Joint Program Committee of Interreg Programs with EU countries and chaired meetings with partners from the European Commission and Finland.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's In Regional Policy and Management

Sep 2015 - Jun 2019

Russian Presidential Academy of National Economy and Public Administration (RANEPA), Moscow, Russia (graduated with honors)

Master's in Social Science (Population and Development)

Sep 2019 - Jun 2021

National Research University Higher School of Economics, Moscow, Russia

Yandex Practicum - Data Science
Bootcamp

Nov 2022 - Jul 2023

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Python for Data Analysis and Data Science, SQL, Looker, Clicdata, Tableau, Power BI, chatbots
- Languages: English C1, Spanish C1.
- Awards: Full scholarship for Bachelor's and Master's program awarded for successful completion of Higher School of Economics Student Olympiad and National Student Olympiad 'I am Professional'.